Hello traders, in today's video I am going to
share 10 companies that have
announced a massive dividend here. So
guys, our number one company is
Bharat Electronics and its current
market price is
288. Where the company has announced a dividend of 80 paise per share,
all of you will be
given a dividend of 80 paise per share
and the exact and recorded date of giving this dividend is
still upcoming, so
as soon as this company announces the exact and recorded date,
you will be updated, so you must
subscribe to the channel. Our next
company is PTC India and its current
market price is 226 and the company is going to
announce its dividend and result here and the
board of directors meeting of the company
regarding the dividend and result will be held
here on 30th May. So guys, our
next company is Filter Consultants and its
current market price is 111. This is the winning
company where it is going to announce its dividend and
result.  On 27th
May, our fourth number company IC II
Lord and its current market price
is
1662 and the company has
announced to give share dividend at ₹. All of you will be
given a dividend of ₹ on every share and the
exact and recorded date of giving this dividend will be on 7th
June. Fifth
number company is Bakaaj Foods and its current
market price is
537. The company is going to give share dividend at ₹1 here
and the exact date of giving this dividend will be on
14th June.
Talking about the next company, Page Industries
and its current market price is
35650 and the company has
announced share dividend at ₹10 here.
This means that all of you will be given a dividend of ₹10 on every share and the
exact and recorded date of giving this dividend has been
announced by the company. It is going to be on 31st May.
If you  If you want the benefit of dividend, then
you will have to buy it before its expiry, that is,
you will have to buy this share before 31st May. The
seventh number company is
Petronet LNG and its current market
price is 308. The company has
announced a share dividend of ₹ and the expiry date for
giving this dividend is
in the coming days. So,
subscribe to the channel for updates.
As soon as the company announces the expiry date,
you will be updated. The
next company is Power Grid Corporation of
India and its current market price is
319. The
company has announced a share dividend of ₹ 39 paisa here
and the expiry date for
giving this dividend is
in the coming days. So guys, now let's talk about
our last stock of today,
ITC Limited and its current market
price is 440 and the company has bought it
here.  Share dividend has been announced at ₹ 50 paisa.
All of you will be
given a dividend of ₹ 50 on each share and the company has announced the date of
giving this dividend as well, it is going to be on
4th
June. So that's all for today's video,
if you liked the video then please
like the video and
subscribe to the channel for more updates.